 [
  {
    "numb": 1,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0011' to Decimal",
    "answer": "B) 3",
    "options": [
      "A) 5",
      "B) 3",
      "C) 7",
      "D) 9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 2,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0111' to Decimal",
    "answer": "C) 7",
    "options": [
      "A) 5",
      "B) 3",
      "C) 7",
      "D) 9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 3,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '1000' to Decimal",
    "answer": "A) 8",
    "options": [
      "A) 8",
      "B) 12",
      "C) 14",
      "D) 9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 4,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '1001' to Decimal",
    "answer": "D) 9",
    "options": [
      "A) 5",
      "B) 3",
      "C) 7",
      "D) 9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 5,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0000' to Decimal",
    "answer": "B) 0",
    "options": [
      "A) -2",
      "B) 0",
      "C) 7",
      "D) 9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 6,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0101' to Decimal",
    "answer": "A) 5",
    "options": [
      "A) 5",
      "B) 3",
      "C) 7",
      "D) 9"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 7,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0101 1000' to Decimal",
    "answer": "C) 58",
    "options": [
      "A) 65",
      "B) 53",
      "C) 58",
      "D) 49"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 8,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '1001 0001' to Decimal",
    "answer": "A) 91",
    "options": [
      "A) 91",
      "B) 93",
      "C) 97",
      "D) 92"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 9,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0001 0110' to Decimal",
    "answer": "B) 16",
    "options": [
      "A) 15",
      "B) 16",
      "C) 17",
      "D) 19"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 10,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '1000 0111' to Decimal",
    "answer": "B) 87",
    "options": [
      "A) 85",
      "B) 87",
      "C) 87",
      "D) 99"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 11,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0100 0100' to Decimal",
    "answer": "D) 44",
    "options": [
      "A) 45",
      "B) 43",
      "C) 47",
      "D) 44"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 12,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '1000 0000' to Decimal",
    "answer": "B) 80",
    "options": [
      "A) 85",
      "B) 80",
      "C) 87",
      "D) 86"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 13,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0010 1000 1000' to Decimal",
    "answer": "A) 288",
    "options": [
      "A) 288",
      "B) 293",
      "C) 127",
      "D) 189"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 14,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0011 0100 0001' to Decimal",
    "answer": "B) 341",
    "options": [
      "A) 365",
      "B) 341",
      "C) 297",
      "D) 309"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 15,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '1001 0000 0010' to Decimal",
    "answer": "C) 902",
    "options": [
      "A) 905",
      "B) 963",
      "C) 902",
      "D) 689"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 16,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0111 0110 1000' to Decimal",
    "answer": "C) 768",
    "options": [
      "A) 825",
      "B) 923",
      "C) 768",
      "D) 629"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 17,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '1001 0010 0010' to Decimal",
    "answer": "B) 922",
    "options": [
      "A) 596",
      "B) 922",
      "C) 865",
      "D) 289"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 18,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0101 0111 0101' to Decimal",
    "answer": "D) 575",
    "options": [
      "A) 436",
      "B) 293",
      "C) 795",
      "D) 575"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 19,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '1001 0001 0001' to Decimal",
    "answer": "B) 911",
    "options": [
      "A) 569",
      "B) 911",
      "C) 721",
      "D) 969"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 20,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the BCD '0001 0010 0011' to Decimal",
    "answer": "A) 123",
    "options": [
      "A) 123",
      "B) 163",
      "C) 257",
      "D) 309"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 1,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '5' to BCD",
    "answer": "B) 0101",
    "options": [
      "A) 1101",
      "B) 0101",
      "C) 1101",
      "D) 0010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 2,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '7' to BCD",
    "answer": "A) 0111",
    "options": [
      "A) 0111",
      "B) 0101",
      "C) 1101",
      "D) 0110"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 3,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '3' to BCD",
    "answer": "B) 0011",
    "options": [
      "A) 1010",
      "B) 0011",
      "C) 0100",
      "D) 1001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 4,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '9' to BCD",
    "answer": "C) 1001",
    "options": [
      "A) 1101",
      "B) 1011",
      "C) 1001",
      "D) 1010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 5,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '0' to BCD",
    "answer": "B) 0000",
    "options": [
      "A) 0001",
      "B) 0000",
      "C) 0010",
      "D) 0100"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 6,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '15' to BCD",
    "answer": "B) 0001 0101",
    "options": [
      "A) 1001 0001",
      "B) 0001 0101",
      "C) 1011 0100",
      "D) 0110 0101 "
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 7,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '22' to BCD",
    "answer": "D) 0010 0010",
    "options": [
      "A) 1000 1000",
      "B) 1010 0101",
      "C) 1001 0100",
      "D) 0010 0010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 8,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '43' to BCD",
    "answer": "B) 0100 0011",
    "options": [
      "A) 1001 0001",
      "B) 0100 0011",
      "C) 1101 0110",
      "D) 1100 1011"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 9,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '37' to BCD",
    "answer": "A) 0011 0111",
    "options": [
      "A) 0011 0111",
      "B) 1000 1001",
      "C) 1010 1010",
      "D) 0101 0100"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 10,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '72' to BCD",
    "answer": "D) 0111 0010",
    "options": [
      "A) 0101 0001",
      "B) 1010 1001",
      "C) 1010 1100",
      "D) 0111 0010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 11,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '98' to BCD",
    "answer": "B) 1001 1000",
    "options": [
      "A) 1010 0010",
      "B) 1001 1000",
      "C) 1111 0000",
      "D) 1010 1010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 12,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '84' to BCD",
    "answer": "A) 1000 0100",
    "options": [
      "A) 1000 0100",
      "B) 1101 0110",
      "C) 1101 0101",
      "D) 0010 1000"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 13,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '567' to BCD",
    "answer": "B) 0101 0110 0111",
    "options": [
      "A) 1010 1011 1011",
      "B) 0101 0110 0111",
      "C) 0100 0011 1011",
      "D) 1001 1011 1101"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 14,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '923' to BCD",
    "answer": "D) 1001 0010 0011",
    "options": [
      "A) 1011 0010 1100",
      "B) 0110 1001 1010",
      "C) 1101 1010 1110",
      "D) 1001 0010 0011"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 15,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '743' to BCD",
    "answer": "C) 0111 0100 0011",
    "options": [
      "A) 1011 0101 0111",
      "B) 1101 0110 1011",
      "C) 0111 0100 0011",
      "D) 1101 1011 1110"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 16,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '839' to BCD",
    "answer": "B) 1000 0011 1001",
    "options": [
      "A) 1001 1110 0111",
      "B) 1000 0011 1001",
      "C) 1101 1101 1101",
      "D) 0101 0001 0001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 17,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '938' to BCD",
    "answer": "A) 1001 0011 1000",
    "options": [
      "A) 1001 0011 1000",
      "B) 1100 1000 0100",
      "C) 1001 0111 0110",
      "D) 1000 1000 1001"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 18,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '475' to BCD",
    "answer": "B) 0100 0111 0101",
    "options": [
      "A) 1101 1010 1001",
      "B) 0100 0111 0101",
      "C) 1101 1011 0010",
      "D) 1101 1010 1010"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 19,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '285' to BCD",
    "answer": "D) 0010 1000 0101",
    "options": [
      "A) 1001 1001 0011",
      "B) 0011 0001 0001",
      "C) 1100 1000 1000",
      "D) 0010 1000 0101"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 20,
    "type": "Multiple Choices",
    "question": "Convert the Decimal '625' to BCD",
    "answer": "A) 0110 0010 0101",
    "options": [
      "A) 0110 0010 0101",
      "B) 1100 1001 0110",
      "C) 0101 0100 1101",
      "D) 1101 0100 1010"
    ]
  }
]